<metadata>
	<idinfo>
		<citation>
			<citeinfo>
				<origin>Jaffe, Melissa R.</origin>
				<origin>Scott, Joe H.</origin>
				<origin>Callahan, Michael N.</origin>
				<origin>Dillon, Gregory K.</origin>
				<origin>Karau, Eva C.</origin>
				<origin>Lazarz, Mitchell T.</origin>
				<pubdate>2024</pubdate>
				<title>Wildfire Risk to Communities: Spatial datasets of wildfire risk for populated areas in the United States</title>
				<geoform>raster digital data</geoform>
				<pubinfo>
					<pubplace>Fort Collins, CO</pubplace>
					<publish>Forest Service Research Data Archive</publish>
				</pubinfo>
				<othercit>This dataset represents Housing Unit Risk for CONUS.</othercit>
				<edition>2nd</edition>
				<onlink>https://doi.org/10.2737/RDS-2020-0060-2</onlink>
			</citeinfo>
		</citation>
		<descript>
			<purpose>The geospatial data products described and distributed here are part of the Wildfire Risk to Communities project. This project was directed by Congress in the 2018 Consolidated Appropriations Act (i.e., 2018 Omnibus Act, H.R. 1625, Section 210: Wildfire Hazard Severity Mapping) to help U.S. communities understand components of their relative wildfire risk profile, the nature and effects of wildfire risk, and actions communities can take to mitigate risk. The first edition of these data represented the first time wildfire risk to communities had been mapped nationally with consistent methodology. They provided foundational information for comparing the relative wildfire risk among populated communities in the United States. In this version, the 2nd edition, we use improved modeling and mapping methodology and updated input data to generate the current suite of products.</purpose>
			<abstract>This dataset represents housing unit risk for the extent of the continental Unitied States (CONUS). It is part of the Wildfire Risk to Communities: Spatial datasets of wildfire risk for populated areas in the United States publication. Housing Unit Risk is a 30-m raster that integrates all four primary elements of wildfire risk - likelihood, intensity, susceptibility, and exposure - on pixels where housing unit density is greater than zero.

National wildfire hazard datasets of annual burn probability and fire intensity, generated by the USDA Forest Service, Rocky Mountain Research Station and Pyrologix LLC, form the foundation of the Wildfire Risk to Communities data. Vegetation and wildland fuels data from LANDFIRE 2020 (version 2.2.0) were used as input to two different but related geospatial fire simulation systems. Annual burn probability was produced with the USFS geospatial fire simulator (FSim) at a relatively coarse cell size of 270 meters (m). To bring the burn probability raster data down to a finer resolution more useful for assessing hazard and risk to communities, we upsampled them to the native 30 m resolution of the LANDFIRE fuel and vegetation data. In this upsampling process, we also spread values of modeled burn probability into developed areas represented in LANDFIRE fuels data as non-burnable. Burn probability rasters represent landscape conditions as of the end of 2020. Fire intensity characteristics were modeled at 30 m resolution using a process that performs a comprehensive set of FlamMap runs spanning the full range of weather-related characteristics that occur during a fire season and then integrates those runs into a variety of results based on the likelihood of those weather types occurring. Before the fire intensity modeling, the LANDFIRE 2020 data were updated to reflect fuels disturbances occurring in 2021 and 2022. As such, the fire intensity datasets represent landscape conditions as of the end of 2022. These datasets characterizing components of risk across the entire landscape are available in a companion data publication (https://doi.org/10.2737/RDS-2020-0016-2).

The data products in this publication that represent where people live reflect 2020 estimates of housing units and 2021 estimates of population counts from the U.S. Census Bureau, combined with building footprint data from Onegeo and USA Structures, both reflecting 2022 conditions.   

Please refer to the metadata documentation for the main publication (https://doi.org/10.2737/RDS-2020-0060-2) for detailed process steps, tools and references related to this dataset. Additional methodology documentation is provided in a methods document (\Supplements\WildfireRiskToCommunities_V2_Methods_PopulatedAreas.pdf) packaged in the data downoad.</abstract>
			<supplinf>See the Wildfire Risk to Communities website at https://www.wildfirerisk.org for complete project information and an interactive web application for exploring some of the datasets published here. We deliver the data here as zip files by U.S. state (including AK and HI), and for the full extent of the continental U.S.
	  
This data publication is a second edition and represents an update to any previous versions of Wildfire Risk to Communities risk datasets published by the USDA Forest Service. There are two companion data publications that are part of the WRC 2.0 data update: one that characterizes landscape-wide wildfire hazard and risk for the nation (Scott et al. 2024, https://doi.org/10.2737/RDS-2020-0016-2), and one that delineates wildfire risk reduction zones and provides tabular summaries of wildfire hazard and risk raster datasets (Dillon et al. 2024, https://doi.org/10.2737/RDS-2024-0030).</supplinf>
		</descript>
		<timeperd>
			<timeinfo>
				<mdattim>
					<sngdate>
						<caldate>2020</caldate>
					</sngdate>
					<sngdate>
						<caldate>2021</caldate>
					</sngdate>
					<sngdate>
						<caldate>2022</caldate>
					</sngdate>
				</mdattim>
			</timeinfo>
			<current>Ground condition</current>
		</timeperd>
		<status>
			<update>As needed</update>
			<progress>Complete</progress>
		</status>
		<spdom>
			<bounding>
				<eastbc>-73.63564534</eastbc>
				<northbc>48.75152842</northbc>
				<westbc>-128.3869213</westbc>
				<southbc>22.50362397</southbc>
			</bounding>
		</spdom>
		<keywords>
			<theme>
				<themekt>ISO 19115 Topic Categories</themekt>
				<themekey>environment</themekey>
				<themekey>geoscientificInformation</themekey>
				<themekey>society</themekey>
				<themekey>structure</themekey>
			</theme>
			<theme>
				<themekt>National Research &amp; Development Taxonomy</themekt>
				<themekey>Ecology, Ecosystems, &amp; Environment</themekey>
				<themekey>Fire</themekey>
				<themekey>Fire detection</themekey>
				<themekey>Fire ecology</themekey>
				<themekey>Fire effects on environment</themekey>
				<themekey>Fire suppression, pre-suppression</themekey>
				<themekey>Prescribed fire</themekey>
				<themekey>Environment and People</themekey>
				<themekey>Forest management</themekey>
				<themekey>Landscape management</themekey>
			</theme>
			<theme>
				<themekt>None</themekt>
				<themekey>burn probability</themekey>
				<themekey>hazard</themekey>
				<themekey>fuels management</themekey>
				<themekey>fire suppression</themekey>
				<themekey>fire likelihood</themekey>
				<themekey>fire planning</themekey>
				<themekey>risk assessment</themekey>
				<themekey>wildfire hazard potential</themekey>
			</theme>
			<place>
				<placekt>None</placekt>
				<placekey>conterminous United States</placekey>
				<placekey>United States</placekey>
				<placekey>CONUS</placekey>
			</place>
		</keywords>
		<accconst>None</accconst>
		<useconst>These data were collected using funding from the U.S. Government and can be used without additional permissions or fees. If you use these data in a publication, presentation, or other research product please use the following citation: 

Jaffe, Melissa R.; Scott, Joe H.; Callahan, Michael N.; Dillon, Gregory K.; Karau, Eva C.; Lazarz, Mitchell T. 2024. Wildfire Risk to Communities: Spatial datasets of wildfire risk for populated areas in the United States. Fort Collins, CO: Forest Service Research Data Archive. https://doi.org/10.2737/RDS-2020-0060-2

The datasets presented here are the product of modeling, and as such carry an inherent degree of error and uncertainty. Users are strongly encouraged to read and fully comprehend the metadata and other available documentation prior to data use. No warranty is made by the Originator as to the accuracy, reliability, or completeness of these data for individual use or aggregate use with other data, or for purposes not intended by the Originator. These datasets are intended to provide nationally-consistent information for the purpose of comparing relative wildfire risk among communities nationally or within a state or county. Data included here are not intended to replace locally-calibrated state, regional, or local risk assessments where they exist. It is the responsibility of the user to be familiar with the value, assumptions, and limitations of these national data publications. Managers and planners must evaluate these data according to the scale and requirements specific to their needs. Spatial information may not meet National Map Accuracy Standards. This information may be updated without notification.</useconst>
		<ptcontac>
			<cntinfo>
				<cntorgp>
					<cntorg>USDA Forest Service, Fire Modeling Institute (FMI)</cntorg>
				</cntorgp>
				<cntaddr>
					<addrtype>mailing and physical</addrtype>
					<address>Missoula Fire Sciences Laboratory</address>
					<address>5775 US Hwy 10 W</address>
					<city>Missoula</city>
					<state>MT</state>
					<postal>59808</postal>
					<country>USA</country>
				</cntaddr>
				<cntvoice>406-329-4836</cntvoice>
				<cntemail>eva.c.karau@usda.gov</cntemail>
			</cntinfo>
		</ptcontac>
		<datacred>Funding for this project provided by USDA Forest Service, Fire and Aviation Management. Funding also provided by USDA Forest Service, Fire Modeling Institute, which is part of the Rocky Mountain Research Station, Fire, Fuel and Smoke Science Program. Work on dataset development was primarily completed by Pyrologix, LLC under contract with the USDA Forest Service, Fire Modeling Institute.</datacred>
	</idinfo>
	<dataqual>
		<attracc>
			<attraccr>Several of the datasets described here are derived from wildfire simulation modeling, and their exact accuracy cannot be measured. These include Building Exposure Type, Housing Unit Exposure, Housing Unit Impact, and Housing Unit Risk. They are intended to be relative measures of wildfire risk for planning purposes. The FSim burn probability dataset was objectively evaluated and calibrated against historical wildfire occurrence statistics within136 distinct regions of contemporary wildfire activity (pyromes) across the United States (Short et.al 2020). See Dillon et al. (2023) for a more detailed description of FSim calibration. Some LANDFIRE fuels and vegetation data used as inputs have also been evaluated for efficacy and calibrated to meet the objectives of LANDFIRE. More information can be found at: https://www.landfire.gov/lf_evaluation.php. No explicit evaluation or calibration is possible for the WildEST (FlamMap-based) intensity datasets, however the LANDFIRE FBFM is an important input which has been evaluated, and the WildEST modeling system is rooted in established fire behavior models and methods (see Finney 2006, and Scott 2020). As such, modeled intensity is considered a robust characterization as input to the flame length probability products.

Datasets included here describing population, buildings and housing units were creating using the combination of U.S. Census datasets and building footprints. Accuracy analyses have not been completed for WRC2.0 Populated Areas datasets. We did, however, perform an analysis on population and housing unit data created for WRC 1.0, carefully checking to ensure that numbers of homes and people derived similarly to the datasets in this publication generally agreed with published population estimates (Scott et. al 2020).

Dillon, Gregory K.; Scott, Joe H.; Jaffe, Melissa R.; Olszewski, Julia H.; Vogler, Kevin C.; Finney, Mark A.; Short, Karen C.; Riley, Karin L.; Grenfell, Isaac C.; Jolly, W. Matthew; Brittain, Stuart. 2023. Spatial datasets of probabilistic wildfire risk components for the United States (270m). 3rd Edition. Fort Collins, CO: Forest Service Research Data Archive. https://doi.org/10.2737/RDS-2016-0034-3  

Finney, Mark A. 2006. An overview of FlamMap fire modeling capabilities. In: Andrews, Patricia L.; Butler, Bret W., comps. 2006. Fuels management-how to measure success: conference proceedings. 28-30 March 2006 in Portland, OR. Proceedings. RMRS-P-41. Fort Collins, CO: U.S. Department of Agriculture, Forest Service, Rocky Mountain Research Station. p. 213-220. https://www.fs.usda.gov/research/treesearch/25948
 
Scott, Joe H. 2020. A deterministic method for generating flame-length probabilities. In: Hood, Sharon M.; Drury, Stacy; Steelman, Toddi; Steffens, Ron, eds. 2020. Proceedings of the fire continuum-preparing for the future of wildland fire. 2018 May 21-24 in Missoula, MT. Proceedings. RMRS-P-78. Fort Collins, CO: U.S. Department of Agriculture, Forest Service, Rocky Mountain Research Station. p. 195-205. https://www.fs.usda.gov/research/treesearch/62336

Scott, Joe H.; Brough, April M.; Gilbertson-Day, Julie W.; Dillon, Gregory K.; Moran, Christopher. 2020. Wildfire Risk to Communities: Spatial datasets of wildfire risk for populated areas in the United States. Fort Collins, CO: Forest Service Research Data Archive. https://doi.org/10.2737/RDS-2020-0060

Short, Karen C.; Grenfell, Isaac C.; Riley, Karin L.; Vogler, Kevin C. 2020. Pyromes of the conterminous United States. Fort Collins, CO: Forest Service Research Data Archive. https://doi.org/10.2737/RDS-2020-0020
</attraccr>
			<qattracc>
				<attraccv>Unknown</attraccv>
				<attracce>Quantitative accuracy cannot be evaluated.</attracce>
			</qattracc>
		</attracc>
		<logic>Pixel values in this Housing Unit Risk dataset for CONUS are between 0 and 7,294,316.
.
</logic>
		<complete>All pixels that are part of the land and water of the United States have valid non-negative values.</complete>
		<lineage>
			<procstep>
				<procdesc>Please refer to the metadata documentation for the main publication (https://doi.org/10.2737/RDS-2020-0060-2) for detailed process steps, tools and references related to this dataset. Additional methodology documentation is provided in a methods document (\Supplements\WildfireRiskToCommunities_V2_Methods_PopulatedAreas.pdf) packaged in the data downoad.</procdesc>
				<procdate>Unknown</procdate>
			</procstep>
		</lineage>
	</dataqual>
	<spdoinfo>
		<direct>Raster</direct>
		<rastinfo>
			<rasttype>Pixel</rasttype>
			<rowcount>101538</rowcount>
			<colcount>156335</colcount>
			<rastxsz Sync="TRUE">30.000000</rastxsz><rastysz Sync="TRUE">30.000000</rastysz><rastbpp Sync="TRUE">32</rastbpp><vrtcount Sync="TRUE">1</vrtcount><rastorig Sync="TRUE">Upper Left</rastorig><rastcmap Sync="TRUE">FALSE</rastcmap><rastcomp Sync="TRUE">LZ77</rastcomp><rastband Sync="TRUE">1</rastband><rastdtyp Sync="TRUE">pixel codes</rastdtyp><rastifor Sync="TRUE">FGDBR</rastifor><rastplyr Sync="TRUE">TRUE</rastplyr></rastinfo>
	</spdoinfo>
	<spref>
		<horizsys>
			<planar>
				<planci>
					<coordrep>
						<absres>30</absres>
						<ordres>30.00</ordres>
					</coordrep>
					<plance>Row and Column</plance>
					<plandu>Meters</plandu>
				</planci>
			</planar>
			<geodetic>
				<ellips>Geodetic Reference System 80</ellips>
				<semiaxis>6378137.0000</semiaxis>
				<horizdn>North American Datum of 1983</horizdn>
				<denflat>298.25722210</denflat>
			</geodetic>
		</horizsys>
	</spref>
	<eainfo>
		<overview>
			<eaover>Continuous integer values of housing unit risk. Values for the United States are between 0 and 7,294,396.


</eaover>
			<eadetcit>Jaffe, Melissa R.; Scott, Joe H.; Callahan, Michael N.; Dillon, Gregory K.; Karau, Eva C.; Lazarz, Mitchell T. 2024. Wildfire Risk to Communities: Spatial datasets of wildfire risk for populated areas in the United States. Fort Collins, CO: Forest Service Research Data Archive. https://doi.org/10.2737/RDS-2020-0060-2
</eadetcit>
		</overview>
		<detailed Name="housing_unit_risk.csv"><enttyp><enttypl Sync="TRUE">housing_unit_risk.csv</enttypl><enttypt Sync="TRUE">Table</enttypt><enttypc Sync="TRUE">0</enttypc></enttyp><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">Value</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">Value</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">Integer</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">4</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">0</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">Count</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">Count</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">Double</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">8</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">0</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale></attr></detailed></eainfo>
	<distinfo>
		<resdesc>RDS-2020-0060-2</resdesc>
		<distrib>
			<cntinfo>
				<cntorgp>
					<cntorg>USDA Forest Service, Research and Development</cntorg>
				</cntorgp>
				<cntaddr>
					<addrtype>mailing and physical</addrtype>
					<address>240 West Prospect Road</address>
					<city>Fort Collins</city>
					<state>CO</state>
					<postal>80526</postal>
					<country>USA</country>
				</cntaddr>
				<cntvoice>see Contact Instructions</cntvoice>
				<cntpos>Research Data Archivist
</cntpos>
				<cntinst>This contact information was current as of April 2024. For current information see Contact Us page on: https://doi.org/10.2737/RDS.</cntinst>
			</cntinfo>
		</distrib>
		<stdorder>
			<digform>
				<digtinfo>
					<formvern>2024</formvern>
					<formname>TIFF</formname>
					<formcont>32-bit signed integer; LZW compression; pyramids: levels 9, Nearest Neighbor resampling</formcont>
					<filedec>Files zipped using the zipfile module in Python 2.7.16 (.ZIP file format version 6.3.6)</filedec>
				</digtinfo>
				<digtopt>
					<onlinopt>
						<computer>
							<networka>
								<networkr>https://doi.org/10.2737/RDS-2020-0060-2</networkr>
							</networka>
						</computer>
					</onlinopt>
				</digtopt>
			</digform>
			<fees>None</fees>
		</stdorder>
		<distliab>Metadata documents have been reviewed for accuracy and completeness. Unless otherwise stated, all data and related materials are considered to satisfy the quality standards relative to the purpose for which the data were collected. However, neither the author, the Archive, nor any part of the federal government can assure the reliability or suitability of these data for a particular purpose. The act of distribution shall not constitute any such warranty, and no responsibility is assumed for a user's application of these data or related materials.

The metadata, data, or related materials may be updated without notification. If a user believes errors are present in the metadata, data or related materials, please use the information in (1) Identification Information: Point of Contact, (2) Metadata Reference: Metadata Contact, or (3) Distribution Information: Distributor to notify the author or the Archive of the issues.</distliab>
	</distinfo>
	<metainfo>
		<metd>20240518</metd>
		<metc>
			<cntinfo>
				<cntorgp>
					<cntorg>USDA Forest Service, Fire Modeling Institute (FMI)</cntorg>
				</cntorgp>
				<cntaddr>
					<addrtype>mailing and physical</addrtype>
					<address>Missoula Fire Sciences Laboratory</address>
					<address>5775 US Hwy 10 W</address>
					<city>Missoula</city>
					<state>MT</state>
					<postal>59808</postal>
					<country>USA</country>
				</cntaddr>
				<cntvoice>406-329-4836</cntvoice>
				<cntemail>eva.c.karau@usda.gov</cntemail>
			</cntinfo>
		</metc>
		<metstdn>FGDC Content Standard for Digital Geospatial Metadata</metstdn>
		<metstdv>FGDC-STD-001.1-1999</metstdv>
	</metainfo>
	<dataIdInfo><envirDesc Sync="TRUE">Microsoft Windows 10 Version 10.0 (Build 22631) ; Esri ArcGIS 13.4.0.55405</envirDesc><dataLang><languageCode value="eng" Sync="TRUE"></languageCode><countryCode value="USA" Sync="TRUE"></countryCode></dataLang><idCitation><resTitle Sync="TRUE">housing_unit_risk.csv</resTitle><presForm><PresFormCd value="001" Sync="TRUE"></PresFormCd></presForm></idCitation><spatRpType><SpatRepTypCd value="002" Sync="TRUE"></SpatRepTypCd></spatRpType><dataExt><geoEle><GeoBndBox esriExtentType="search"><exTypeCode Sync="TRUE">1</exTypeCode><westBL Sync="TRUE">-95.867984</westBL><eastBL Sync="TRUE">-82.445924</eastBL><northBL Sync="TRUE">49.388220</northBL><southBL Sync="TRUE">43.056169</southBL></GeoBndBox></geoEle></dataExt></dataIdInfo><mdLang><languageCode value="eng" Sync="TRUE"></languageCode><countryCode value="USA" Sync="TRUE"></countryCode></mdLang><Esri><DataProperties><itemProps><itemName Sync="TRUE">housing_unit_risk.csv</itemName><imsContentType Sync="TRUE">005</imsContentType><nativeExtBox><westBL Sync="TRUE">10605.000000</westBL><eastBL Sync="TRUE">1004925.000000</eastBL><southBL Sync="TRUE">2294835.000000</southBL><northBL Sync="TRUE">2930835.000000</northBL><exTypeCode Sync="TRUE">1</exTypeCode></nativeExtBox><itemLocation><linkage Sync="TRUE">file://\\MI403-CS3Q7M3\C$\Users\rswaty\Documents\northwoods\inputs\housing_unit_risk.csv</linkage><protocol Sync="TRUE">Local Area Network</protocol></itemLocation><itemSize Sync="TRUE">0.000</itemSize></itemProps><coordRef><type Sync="TRUE">Projected</type><geogcsn Sync="TRUE">GCS_North_American_1983</geogcsn><csUnits Sync="TRUE">Linear Unit: Meter (1.000000)</csUnits><projcsn Sync="TRUE">NAD_1983_Contiguous_USA_Albers</projcsn><peXml Sync="TRUE">&lt;ProjectedCoordinateSystem xsi:type='typens:ProjectedCoordinateSystem' xmlns:xsi='http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance' xmlns:xs='http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema' xmlns:typens='http://www.esri.com/schemas/ArcGIS/3.4.0'&gt;&lt;WKT&gt;PROJCS[&amp;quot;NAD_1983_Contiguous_USA_Albers&amp;quot;,GEOGCS[&amp;quot;GCS_North_American_1983&amp;quot;,DATUM[&amp;quot;D_North_American_1983&amp;quot;,SPHEROID[&amp;quot;GRS_1980&amp;quot;,6378137.0,298.257222101]],PRIMEM[&amp;quot;Greenwich&amp;quot;,0.0],UNIT[&amp;quot;Degree&amp;quot;,0.0174532925199433]],PROJECTION[&amp;quot;Albers&amp;quot;],PARAMETER[&amp;quot;False_Easting&amp;quot;,0.0],PARAMETER[&amp;quot;False_Northing&amp;quot;,0.0],PARAMETER[&amp;quot;Central_Meridian&amp;quot;,-96.0],PARAMETER[&amp;quot;Standard_Parallel_1&amp;quot;,29.5],PARAMETER[&amp;quot;Standard_Parallel_2&amp;quot;,45.5],PARAMETER[&amp;quot;Latitude_Of_Origin&amp;quot;,23.0],UNIT[&amp;quot;Meter&amp;quot;,1.0],AUTHORITY[&amp;quot;EPSG&amp;quot;,5070]]&lt;/WKT&gt;&lt;XOrigin&gt;-16901100&lt;/XOrigin&gt;&lt;YOrigin&gt;-6972200&lt;/YOrigin&gt;&lt;XYScale&gt;266467840.99085236&lt;/XYScale&gt;&lt;ZOrigin&gt;-100000&lt;/ZOrigin&gt;&lt;ZScale&gt;10000&lt;/ZScale&gt;&lt;MOrigin&gt;-100000&lt;/MOrigin&gt;&lt;MScale&gt;10000&lt;/MScale&gt;&lt;XYTolerance&gt;0.001&lt;/XYTolerance&gt;&lt;ZTolerance&gt;0.001&lt;/ZTolerance&gt;&lt;MTolerance&gt;0.001&lt;/MTolerance&gt;&lt;HighPrecision&gt;true&lt;/HighPrecision&gt;&lt;WKID&gt;5070&lt;/WKID&gt;&lt;LatestWKID&gt;5070&lt;/LatestWKID&gt;&lt;/ProjectedCoordinateSystem&gt;</peXml></coordRef><lineage><Process ToolSource="c:\program files\arcgis\pro\Resources\ArcToolbox\toolboxes\Data Management Tools.tbx\Clip" Date="20250708" Time="144655">Clip HURisk_CONUS.tif "10625.9212583442 2294844.13613895 1004930.97145059 2930823.02922067" D:\northwoods_arc\northwoods.gdb\HURisk_CONUS_Clip northwoods -2147483648 ClippingGeometry NO_MAINTAIN_EXTENT</Process><Process ToolSource="c:\program files\arcgis\pro\Resources\ArcToolbox\toolboxes\Conversion Tools.tbx\ExportTable" Date="20250708" Time="145549">ExportTable HURisk_CONUS_Clip C:\Users\rswaty\Documents\northwoods\inputs\housing_unit_risk.csv # NOT_USE_ALIAS "Value "Value" false true false 4 Long 0 0,First,#,HURisk_CONUS_Clip,Value,-1,-1;Count "Count" false true false 8 Double 0 0,First,#,HURisk_CONUS_Clip,Count,-1,-1" #</Process></lineage></DataProperties><SyncDate>20250708</SyncDate><SyncTime>14554900</SyncTime><ModDate>20250708</ModDate><ModTime>14554900</ModTime></Esri><distInfo><distFormat><formatName Sync="TRUE">Text File</formatName></distFormat><distTranOps><transSize Sync="TRUE">0.000</transSize></distTranOps></distInfo><mdHrLv><ScopeCd value="007" Sync="TRUE"></ScopeCd></mdHrLv><mdHrLvName Sync="TRUE">non-geographic dataset</mdHrLvName><refSysInfo><RefSystem><refSysID><identCode code="5070" Sync="TRUE"></identCode><idCodeSpace Sync="TRUE">EPSG</idCodeSpace><idVersion Sync="TRUE">7.4.6(10.1.0)</idVersion></refSysID></RefSystem></refSysInfo><mdDateSt Sync="TRUE">20250708</mdDateSt></metadata>
